<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coquitlam School Board Trustee on Barb Hobson</title>
    <link>https://barbhobson.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coquitlam School Board Trustee on Barb Hobson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language><atom:link href="https://barbhobson.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Career</title>
      <link>https://barbhobson.ca/about/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbhobson.ca/about/career/</guid>
      <description>About School Trustee Community Career  Administration &amp;amp; Organization
 Dependable Team Leader and Member Considerable management experience  Communication
 Strong verbal communication skills Excellent written communication skills Excellent interpersonal skills  Areas of Knowledge and Strength
 Expert on corporate governance Organization of meetings and events Chairing meetings Media relations Policy development and compliance  Professional Experience As a member of the President&amp;rsquo;s Executive Council and de facto Corporate Secretary at BCIT, I advised the Board and the President on governance and procedural issues, organized and assisted in setting agendas for all meetings of the Board and committees of the Board, including the Governance, Audit &amp;amp; Finance, Human Resources and Tributes Committees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://barbhobson.ca/about/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbhobson.ca/about/community/</guid>
      <description>About School Trustee Community Career    In her role as President of Place des Arts, Barb thanks attendees for supporting fundraising efforts.   As an active member of our community I continue to be passionate about educating all students to the best of their abilities. I am well connected in the community and have worked with all levels of government for more than 30 years.
Currently, in addition to being an elected school trustee, I serve as President of the Board of Place des Arts and Community Service Director of the Rotary Club of Coquitlam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://barbhobson.ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbhobson.ca/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>School Trustee</title>
      <link>https://barbhobson.ca/about/trustee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbhobson.ca/about/trustee/</guid>
      <description>About School Trustee Community Career    Barb representing SD. 43 at the BCSTA&amp;#39;s 2018 AGM.   As an active member of the School Board, I work with our partner groups as well as 5 local mayors and their councils, our 4 local MLA’s and the provincial government. The school district’s operating budget of close to $375 million is a focus of mine. I have been diligent in monitoring revenues and expenditures on a continuous basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Successes</title>
      <link>https://barbhobson.ca/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barbhobson.ca/success/</guid>
      <description>Smiling Creek Elementary opened Sept 4, 2018 bringing 430 new student spaces to Burke Mountain.   Since being elected in 2014 our Board has been successful in:
 Maintaining graduation rates that are #2 province wide, nearly 7% higher than the Provincial average. Repaying $13.4 Million of debt. Building Smiling Creek Elementary, planning an additional elementary and a combined middle/secondary and purchasing land for five schools on Burke Mountain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
