<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Barb Hobson</title><link>http://barbhobson.ca/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Barb Hobson</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><atom:link href="http://barbhobson.ca/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Career</title><link>http://barbhobson.ca/about/career/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://barbhobson.ca/about/career/</guid><description>About School Trustee Community Career &#34;I have had the pleasure of working with Barb for over five years and during that time I have found her to have the utmost integrity. Barb is a consummate professional.&#34;
Dr. Tony Knowles
Former President,
British Columbia Institute of Technology Summary of Skills Administration &amp;amp; Organization
Dependable Team Leader and Member Considerable management experience Communication
Strong verbal communication skills Excellent written communication skills Excellent interpersonal skills Areas of Knowledge and Strength</description></item><item><title>Community</title><link>http://barbhobson.ca/about/community/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://barbhobson.ca/about/community/</guid><description>About School Trustee Community Career In her role as President of Place des Arts, Barb thanks attendees for supporting fundraising efforts. As an active member of our community I continue to be passionate about educating all students to the best of their abilities. I am well connected in the community and have worked with all levels of government for more than 30 years.
Currently, in addition to being an elected school trustee, I serve as President of the Board of Place des Arts and Community Service Director of the Rotary Club of Coquitlam.</description></item><item><title>School Trustee</title><link>http://barbhobson.ca/about/trustee/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://barbhobson.ca/about/trustee/</guid><description>About School Trustee Community Career Barb representing SD. 43 at the BCSTA&amp;#39;s 2018 AGM. As an active member of the School Board, I work with our partner groups as well as 5 local mayors and their councils, our 4 local MLA’s and the provincial government. The school district’s operating budget of close to $375 million is a focus of mine. I have been diligent in monitoring revenues and expenditures on a continuous basis.</description></item></channel></rss>